EDWARD MANN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

EMAIL THE@EDDMANN.COM WEB EDDMANN.COM MOBILE 07517 335305

PROFILE

My passion is invested in the backend development and consumption of the web. Coupled with this, is the drive to make the next generation of desktop/web application using the latest development processes and ideologies. As a social person the team dynamic appeals to me greatly, giving me the opportunity to work with like-minded people. Through my present employment, since leaving University, I have had the chance to garner experience in both large (new startups) and small-scale (local businesses) application projects. In all scenarios I have invested personal time into researching and blogging about the latest best practices/technologies, which I then work hard to integrate into the development lifecycles I am apart of.

SKILLS

Java Git • Unix • PHPUnit • Behat

PHP MySQL • PostgreSQL • Sphinx

Python Titanium • C# • CodeIgniter

JavaScript ASP.NET • Shell Scripting

EDUCATION

BSc Internet Computing

2008 - 2011

University of Greenwich - London, England

1st Class Honours

* school prize for outstanding achievement

BTEC National Diploma for IT Practitioners

West Kent College - Tonbridge, Kent

Distinction, Distinction, Merit

Secondary School GCSEs

Hugh Christie Tech. College - Tonbridge, Kent

14 Gained A* - C

* maths, english & science included

EXPERIENCE

Atkins Global 2004

Work Experience

Robert Dyas 2006 - 2007

Part-time Sales Assistant

360 Software Solutions 2011 - Present

Web Developer

INTERESTS

As well as computing I have many other outside interests, these include:

- Exploring while travelling
- Playing basketball
- Listening to podcasts
- Watching football
- Black and white film photography

REFERENCES

Available upon request.